Ma'ayan Shuvi

Yahalom 30, Sha'arey Tiquva, Israel 10/18/1991

+972-54-2077266

Maayan.shu.v@gmail.com



Short Bio

I am currently pursuing M.Sc. in Electrical Engineering at Tel-Aviv University, where I work with Prof. Daniel Cohen-Or on Convolutional Neural Network architectures and their applications in Computer Vision, Computer Graphics and their intersection.

I served in the Israeli Defense Intelligence (IDI) for 4 years, as an officer in an operational-technological unit which is responsible for operating imaging satellites, plan their mission and process their images.

Education

M.Sc. in Electrical Engineering, Tel Aviv University 2018-present

Research areas: Deep Learning, Computer Vision, Computer Graphics

Supervision: Prof. Daniel Cohen-Or

GPA: 92.64

B.Sc. in Electrical Engineering, Tel Aviv University 2014-2018

I was selected for direct M.Sc. track program for excellent B.Sc. students.

Specialization on: Communication, Control, Signal processing

GPA: 86.5

Experience

Teacher assistant, Tel-Aviv University, 2018-present

Signals and systems course

Discrete signal processing course

Software engineer, Image processing team, IAI 2017

Student position. Developing a post-processing system for satellite images at Israel Aerospace Industries, space department.

Software QA engineer, Satellite operating team, IAI 2015-2017

Student position. Responsible for validating systems of tracking and monitoring the satellite's equipment and performance in orbit.

Performed manual testing and wrote daily test plans for satellite operation systems.

Product manager, first lieutenant, Satellite unit, IDI 2012-2014

Responsible for characterization, testing and launch of satellite control and operation systems.

Coordinated with the operational unit and IAI, and lead project manager in product development, testing and validation.

Officers course, 2012

Satellite operator, Satellite unit, IDI 2010-2014

Responsible for daily mission planning of satellite operations.

Programming Language experience

Python, Pytorch, MATLAB, C

Languages

Hebrew – mother tongue

English - fluent

Skills

Ambitious, creative, self-learner, people person, responsible